<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>canicodenow</title>
    <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on canicodenow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 21:55:01 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I found some more time to study down the back of the sofa, or &#39;I&#39;ve gone part-time for a year&#39;</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/part-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 21:55:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/part-time/</guid>
      <description>Can I code now? No. Of course not.
Well, I know some stuff but this answer will only be yes when I&amp;rsquo;m employed as a coder, remember? I&amp;rsquo;ll keep asking as that&amp;rsquo;s the whole reason I&amp;rsquo;m doing this. It&amp;rsquo;s hard, but I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit more confident lately.
So what&amp;rsquo;s changed? I said before how hard I found it to study with full-time work. I think I may have solved that one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I&#39;ve made so far</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/things-ive-made/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 21:33:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/things-ive-made/</guid>
      <description>I can say how much I’ve read about web development or how many tutorials I’ve completed, but the real evidence will be things. Things I’ve made that work and that can go on my CV.
So here’s where I’m at in terms of things.
CS50x project(s) In my last blog I mentioned CS50x and why I stopped doing the course. Before that I did make some things, but sadly the course has its own IDE which doesn’t go on to Github, so I don’t have much to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve tried so far, or &#39;ffs, just pick one course!&#39;</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/what-ive-tried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 13:40:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/what-ive-tried/</guid>
      <description>When I decided to learn to code I had no idea how many top quality resources were available – and for free, as well. I wanted to do them all – I thought I could do them all. Even once I’d committed, I was still researching and finding others to do ‘next’. Because smashing through a course about learning to think like a programmer and learning an actual new language would be a breeze, wouldn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My situation, or &#39;so why are you learning to code?’</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/my-situation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/my-situation/</guid>
      <description>It’s about time I followed my goals. My job is fine – I work as a content editor, managing a local authority website – but would I be happy doing that forever? No.
I’m good at it and it pays the bills, but I don’t feel that buzz I’m always told you’re meant to feel. I never knew what I wanted to be growing up, but I’m starting to realise web development is for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m 31. I work full-time in web content, but it doesn’t give me that buzz I’m looking for. Instead, I want to learn web development. My mind works in a logical way and I like to make sure things, just, work.
I set up this site to track my progress – or keep myself in check. Probably the latter, if I’m honest. Certainly not to procrastinate – no way. I’m a writer by nature and experience, so by noting down my problems, my successes, my goals, I think I’ll help my learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can find me on Twitter: @mattdomm_
Or just send me an email:
 Send  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects I&#39;ve completed</title>
      <link>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canicodenow.github.io/folio/projects/</guid>
      <description> 1. Calculator I created a calculator using HTML, CSS and javaScript as part of The Odin Project.
 See it in action
 Take a look at the project on my Github - bugs and todos and all
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>